A Guide to the Papers of the University Librarian, University of Virginia
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Personnel Records
  - Restricted
    - 1981-1982 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:7)
    - 1981-1983 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:8)
    - 1982-1983 Promotion Review Board (Box-folder 15:9)